{
    "id": "e6d75dee20f746a19b43ceb3b02d34f2",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The police were ………………….. everybody’s papers.",
            "description": "Control does not mean check.",
            "answers": [
                "checking",
                "looking",
                "controlling"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The car is difficult to …………………… at high speeds.",
            "description": "To control is to manage.",
            "answers": [
                "check",
                "control",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He looks ………………………",
            "description": "Look is a copular verb. We use adjectives, not adverbs, to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "smart",
                "smartly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She fell ………………………….. on the floor.",
            "description": "We often use adjectives after descriptions with sit, stand, lie and fall.",
            "answers": [
                "unconscious",
                "unconsciously",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The situation seemed ……………………............",
            "description": "Seem is a copular verb. We use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "impossible",
                "impossibly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat ………………………...., waiting for their decision.",
            "description": "We often use adjectives after descriptions with sit, stand, lie and fall.",
            "answers": [
                "motionless",
                "motionlessly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a woman who …………………….. to say what she thinks.",
            "description": "When dare is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "dare",
                "dares",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The old woman ………………………….. to open the door.",
            "description": "The ordinary form of dare is common in negative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't dare",
                "not dared",
                "dared not"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………………. a meeting than a party.",
            "description": "We can use more of before a singular countable noun. This is common in modifying descriptions.",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "more of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You put ……………………….. too much salt in the soup.",
            "description": "We can use much to modify too much.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "quite",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You made ………………………. a lot of mistakes.",
            "description": "A lot can be modified by quite or rather.",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "quite",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We drove ……………………….. up to Madrid in four hours.",
            "description": "Before prepositions referring to movement, right can mean completely or exactly.",
            "answers": [
                "right",
                "rightly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}